# Jagadeesh Sana

#### Contact

**Address** 

Haripuram, AP, 535002

**Phone** 

+91 9573458989

E-mail

sanajagadeesh@outlook.co m

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jagadeesh-sana-b718027

#### **Skills**

Containerisation Tools : Dockers, kubernetes, Pivotal Cloud Foundry

**SCM Tools: GIT** 

Configuration Management : Ansible

Scripting: groovy, Shell

Scripting, Python

Cloud: Amazon web services, GCP

Operating system : Windows, Unix

Scheduling tools : BMC Control-M

Maximo, Remedy, Service now

An experienced Cloud and DevOps engineer with more than 6 years' experience in IT industry seeking to work in a professional, innovative, challenging and friendly environment where I can use/share my skills to the success of the organization.

#### **Work History**

2019-05 -Current

#### **Analyst**

DBS, Hyderabad, Telangana

- Working as CI/CD DevOps Engineer for Frontend,
   Backend and Mobile(los & Android) for a team of
   120 members
- Handling of Deployments to sit/dev/uat environments as per Squad's with automation
- Building of applications with gradel, Maven, python, swift, android and docker
- Creating shared pipeline library for build, scan's and deployment
- Deployment of Micro services to production in PCF with Jenkins pipeline
- Creation of spaces, orgs and services in PCF
- Deployment of applications into Openshift
- Creation of DB and schema for Development needs
- Access management to BitBucket, PCF and project
- Creating reports and sharing with management on build status
- Creating automated scripts for stopping/starting of applications during weekend for cost management
- Using of kubernetes pods for build of applications
- Supported creation of detailed, technical financial models to value potential acquisition targets.
- Planned and conceived computer systems using information engineering, data modeling and structured analysis.

2017-06 -2019-04

#### Cloud/DevOps Engineer

Accenture, Bangalore, Karnataka

- Worked as Cloud/DevOps engineer
- Worked on creation of EC2 instances
- AWS CodeCommit and deployment to EKS
- Using of s3 bucket for logs backup

Code Scanning Tools:
SonarQube, Nexus IQ, Fortify
and Twist Lock

- Creating Ansible playbooks for control-m Agent upgredation on linux servers
- Creating scripts for automatic email of reports from servers

#### 2016-11 -2017-05

#### **Systems Engineer**

CGI, Hyderabad, Telangana

- Worked as BMC Control-M administrator
- Responsible for upgrading Control-M infra from 7.0 to 8.0
- Creating and deployment of Change request's in production and development environment
- Implemented High Availability of Environment
- Automating day to day activity's by creating scripts and scheduling them with Control-M
- Support oncall for critical P1/P2 issues
- Individual contributer for the client Sears having an infra of more than 1000 servers for Control-M

#### 2014-09 -2016-11

#### Systems engineer

IBM, Hyderabad, Telengana

Worked as windows administrator and supported
 11/12 activates for Control-M version 6.4 & 7.0

### **Education**

2013-01

# Bachelor of Engineering: Mechanical Engineering

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU-K) - Visakhapatnam, AP

## **Certifications**

2018-05

AWS Certified SysOps Administrator with certificate number N7Z17KQCBMQQQJ3S